Allen D. Place, Jr. papers, Inclusive: 1989-1998, undated Bulk: 1991-1997
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1991-1997, undated; 3
  - 74th Legislature, 1995-1996; 3
    - Correspondence, 1995; 3
      - Senate Bills (5 of 6), 1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Senate Bills (6 of 6), 1995 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Clipping Service, 1995-1996; 4
      - Erath Day in Austin, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Nuisance Suits, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Prison Expansion, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Juvenile Driving While Intoxicated, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - February, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - March (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - March (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - March (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - March (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - April (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - April (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - April (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - April (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - May (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - May (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - May (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - June (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - June (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - June (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - July (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - July (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - August (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - August (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - August (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - August (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - September (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - September (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - September (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - September (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - October (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - October (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - October (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - October (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - November (1 of 4), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - November (2 of 4), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - November (3 of 4), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - November (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - December (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - December (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - December (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - January (1 of 4), 1996 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - January (2 of 4), 1996 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - January (3 of 4), 1996 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - January (4 of 4), 1996 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - 75th Legislature, 1997; 4
    - General, 1997; 1
      - Policies and Procedures, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - House Daily Reports (1 of 2), 1997 January 13-March 6 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - House Daily Reports (2 of 2), 1997 January 13-March 6 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Senate Daily Reports, 1997 January 13-March 6 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Daily House Calendar (1 of 4), 1997 March 4-June 2 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Daily House Calendar (2 of 4), 1997 March 4-June 2 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Daily House Calendar (3 of 4), 1997 March 4-June 2 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Daily House Calendar (4 of 4), 1997 March 4-June 2 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - House Daily Reports (1 of 3), 1997 March 7-June 1 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - House Daily Reports (2 of 3), 1997 March 7-June 1 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - House Daily Reports (3 of 3), 1997 March 7-June 1 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Senate Daily Reports (1 of 3), 1997 March 7-June 1 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Senate Daily Reports (2 of 3), 1997 March 7-June 1 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Senate Daily Reports (3 of 3), 1997 March 7-June 1 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Bills by Number, 1997; 2
      - Legislative Information System, Bills Sponsored, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - HB 1, State Representative Districts, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - HB 4, Property Tax Relief Plan, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - HB 311, Prosecution of Certain Offenses Involving Firearms, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - HB 312, Tampering with a Witness, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - HB 432, Eligibility for Release on Mandatory Supervision, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - HB 547, Eligibility for Release on Parole of Certain Inmates Serving Sentences for Violent Offenses, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - HB 749, Expunction of Criminal record, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - HB 806, Prosecution of the Offense of Obstruction or Retaliation, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - HB 921, Regarding Statute of Limitations for Certain Sexual Offenses, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - HB 968, Care and Treatment of Game Fowl, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - HB 1185, Fraudulent Exercise of Governmental Functions and Creation or Use of Governmental Documents, and Records; Proving Penalties, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - HB 1230, Juvenile Criminal Detention Facilities, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - HB 1235, Authorizing the Issuance of Revenue Bonds for Certain Public Institutions of Higher Education, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - HB 1391, Free Trial Transcripts for Appeals, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - HB 1452, Poaching; Providing a Penalty, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - HB 1613, Creation of the Offense of Trademark Counterfeiting, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - HB 1649, Thwarting the Compulsory School Attendance Law, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - HB 1650, Creating a Commercial Real Estate Broker’s Lien, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - HB 1747, Procedures for Individuals in the Criminal Justice System with Mental Illness or Mental Retardation, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - HB 1748, Requiring that the Board of Directors of Certain Nonprofit Corporations be Elected at a Statewide Election, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 19)
      - HB 1756, Elimination of Racially Offensive Names Given to Geographical Features, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 20)
      - HB 1779, Real Estate Research Center, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - HB 1941, Poaching, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - HB 2247, Establishment of Central Texas College, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - HB 2323, Repeals and Amendments to Code of Criminal Procedure, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - HB 2341, Certification of Bail Bondsmen, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - HB 2634, Administrative Fees Collected by Community Supervision and Corrections Departments, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - HB 2635, Operation of State Jail Felony Facilities and Supervision of Defendants Convicted of State Jail Felonies, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - HB 2644, Systems and Programs Administered by the Teacher Retirement System of Texas, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - HB 2778, Directing Payment, After Approval, of Certain Miscellaneous Claims and Judgments, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - HB 2825, Use of Inmate and Probationer Labor for State Highway System Projects, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - HB 2826, Regarding Qualifications Required for Appointment as a Community Supervision and Corrections Department Officer, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - HB 2827, Death of an Inmate, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - HB 2828, Public Access to Certain Personal Information about Certain Law Enforcement Personnel, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - HB 2829, Disposition of Restitution Payments Made to Victims of Crime, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - HB 2830, Statutory Lien to Secure the Amount of Restitution to which a Crime Victim is Entitled, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - HB 2836, Providing Individuals Remedies for and Protections against Certain Hateful Acts, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - HB 2837, Filing Fees and Salaries of Judges in the Statutory County Courts of Certain Counties, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - HB 2838, Cash Reserves in Regional Library Systems, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - HB 2918, Extension of a Period of Supervision for a Defendant Charged with or Convicted of Certain Sexual or Sexually Assaultive Offenses, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - HB 3056, Use of a Federal Postcard Application for Early Voting by Mail, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - HB 3347, Actions Against Certain Insurers for Wrongful Failure to Settle a Health Care Liability Claim, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - HB 3348, Definition of Physician in Regards to Medical Liability, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - HB 3349, Contract Management Projects for School Districts, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - HB 3350, Criminal Offenses Applicable to Gambling and Gambling Devices, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - HB 3351, Transfer of the Duties of the State Board of Education, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - HB 3352, Arbitration of Certain Claims Arising from the Construction of Certain State Correctional Facilities, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - HB 3412, Regulation of Corporate Sureties that Write Bail Bonds, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - HB 3533, Procedural Provisions of Health Care Liability Claims, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - HB 3609, Upper Leon River Municipal Water District, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - HCR 105, Comanche County Day at the Capitol, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - HJR 9, Constitutional Amendment to Authorize Comanche County to More than One Precinct for Justices of the Peace and a Single Precinct for Constable, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - HJR 114, Proposing a Constitutional Amendment Relating to the Abolition of the State Board of Education, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - HR 133, Honoring Marion McDaniel, Poet Laureate of Comanche County, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - HR 204, Copperas Cove Day at the State Capitol, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - HR 265, Erath County Day at the State Capitol, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - HR 834, In Memory of Francis C. Ward, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - HR 835, In Memory of Mickey Mantle, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - HR 836, In Memory of Kurtis Gerdel, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - HR 861, In Memory of Helen Graves, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - HR 897, Congratulating the Hamilton High School Golf Team on Class 2A State Championship, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - SB 1, Development and Management of the Water Resources of the State, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - SB 1, Senate Redistricting, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - SB 17, Powers and Duties of County Hospital Authorities, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - SB 35, Minors and Alcohol (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - SB 35, Minors and Alcohol (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - SB 55, Regulation of the Sale, Distribution, and Use of Tobacco Products, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - SB 68, Priority Given to the Hearing of Certain Matters by Trial Courts, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - SB 114, Procedural Requirements and Grounds for Reversing a Criminal Case on Appeal, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - SB 160, Prosecution of the Offense of Tampering with or Fabricating Physical Evidence, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - SB 166, Deferral of Proceedings for Certain Traffic Offenses for Completion of a Driving Safety Course, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - SB 228, Creation of the Offense of Trademark Counterfeiting, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - SB 250, Repeal of Release to Mandatory Supervision and to Parole Procedures, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - SB 298, Juvenile Court Detention Orders, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - SB 467, Prohibiting Certain Complainants Submit to Polygraph Examinations, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - SB 551, Exemption of Certain Persons from Jury Service, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - SB 572, Transfer of the University of Central Texas to the Texas A&M University System, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - SB 573, Creating a Commercial Real Estate Broker’s Lien, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - SB 627, Certification of Bail Bondsmen by the Texas Department of Licensing and Regulation, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - SB 663, Authority of a Judge to Place a Defendant Convicted of a State Jail Felony on Community Supervision, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - SB 674, Prosecution of the Offense of Possession or Promotion of Child Pornography, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - SB 758, Creation of a Graffiti Offense, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - SB 1102, Systems and Programs Administered by the Employees Retirement System of Texas, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - SB 1246, Establishment of a Statewide Rural Health Care System, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - SB 1544, Public Access to Certain Personal Information about Certain Law Enforcement Personnel, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - 75R3390, Eligibility of Inmates Serving Sentences for Indecency with a Child, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - 75R2120, Update Code of Criminal Procedures, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - 75R3504, Extension of a Period of Supervision, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - 75R4122, Ineligibility of Certain Inmates for Release on Mandatory Supervision, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - 75R5139, Punishment for the Criminal Offense of Engaging in a Deceptive Business Practice, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - 75R5180, Operating a Vehicle while Intoxicated, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - 75R6220, Creation of the Offense of Trademark Counterfeiting, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - 75R6586, Officers of the Real Estate Research Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - 75R7027, Value of Property Damaged or Destroyed, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - 75R7031, Real Estate Research Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - 75R7490(1) Extension of Period of Supervision, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - 75R7543, Eligibility Requirements for Voting by Persons Using a Federal Postcard Application, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - 75R12500, Procedures Concerning Early Voting by Persons Using a Federal Postcard Application, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 17)
      - 75R14249, Regarding Death of an Inmate while in Custody, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - 98Y 522, Resolution on Death of Roy William Brannan, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 19)
      - 98Y 584, Resolution on Death of Bradie Blaire Robertson, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - General, undated; 5
    - Photographs, undated (Box 84, Folder 21)